Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory5 Mss.B.B61.inventory05
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents F
  - Fewkes, J. Walter (Box 27)
    - (Memorandum found in March 1925), 1925 Dec. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Sept. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Sept. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - (Enc: Fewkes, J.W. to Hrushevsky, M.), 1927 Mar. 9; 1p.
      - (Fewkes to Cattell), 1927 Nov. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 30; 1p.
    - J.W. Fewkes -- to C.P. Bowditch, 1906 Jan. 10
    - J.W. Fewkes -- to De Lancey Gill, 1917 Dec.; 4p.
    - J.W. Fewkes -- from De Lancey Gill, 1923 June 28
    - J.W. Fewkes -- to W.H. Holmes, 1914 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - J.W. Fewkes -- from F.M. Olbrechts
      (Enc. mentioned not here)
    - J.W. Fewkes -- from F.M. Olbrechts, 1926 Jan. 13
    - J.W. Fewkes -- from E. Sapir, 1920 Apr. 26; 1p.
    - J.W. Fewkes -- to E. Sapir, 1920 May 19; 1p.
    - J.W. Fewkes -- from E. Sapir, 1920 May 21; 1p.
    - J.W. Fewkes -- from E. Sapir, 1920 May 28; 1p.
    - J.W. Fewkes -- to H.E. Sargent, 1923 Feb. 14; 1p.
    - J.W. Fewkes -- from M.E. Sargent
      - (Enc with Sargent, H.E., Apr. 21, 1923)
    - J.W. Fewkes -- from M.E. Sargent, 1923 Apr. 21
    - J.W. Fewkes -- to H.E. Sargent, 1923 Apr. 28; 1p.
    - J.W. Fewkes -- to N. Whymant
      - (Enc. with Whymant, N., May 7, 1926)
    - J.W. Fewkes -- to N. Whymant, (April 19, 1926) 1926 May 5; 1p.
  - Fidelity and Deposit Co., N.Y.C. (Box 27)
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 11; 1p.
  - Fidelity and Deposit Co. of Maryland (Box 27)
    - Fidelity and Deposit Co. of Maryland -- from Uhl, Byrin H., July 9, 1937
      - (Enc. with Boas, F. to Parker, V.L.N., July 28, 1937)
  - Fiebiger (Box 27)
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 28; 1p.
  - Field, Frederick V. (Box 27)
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Sept. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Sept. 10
  - Field, George (Box 27)
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 12; 1p.
  - Field, H. (Box 27)
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 May 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 July 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 10; 1p.
  - Field Museum of Natural History (Box 27)
    (See Laufer, Berthold)
  - Fields, Harold (Box 27)
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 25; 1p.
  - Fiery, M. (Box 27)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 24; 1p.
  - Fife, Robert Herndon (Box 27)
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 30; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 8; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 May 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Oct. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - Robert Herndon Fife -- to Whom it may concern, 1936 Feb. 19; 1p.
  - Figdor, Richard (Box 27)
    - To Boas, 1936 June 27; 1p.
  - The FIGHT FOR RECOGNITION (Box 27)
  - Figueiredo, G. Amazonas de (Box 27)
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb.; 1p.
  - Filene, E.A. (Box 27)
    - From Boas, 1934 Feb. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas
    - (see Brown, P.S., Feb. 7, 1934)
  - Fillmore, John Comfort (Box 27)
    - From Boas, 1894 Jan. 22
    - From Boas, 1894 Jan. 29
    - From Boas, 1894 Feb. 28
    - From Boas, 1894 Apr. 16
    - To Boas, 1893 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1893 Dec. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1893 Dec. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1894 Jan. 25
    - To Boas, 1894 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1894 Feb. 4
    - To Boas, 1894 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1894 Feb. 26
    - To Boas, 1894 Apr. 18
    - To Boas, 1894 Aug. 17
    - To Boas, 1894 Aug. 31
    - To Boas, 1895 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1895 Nov. 7
    - To Boas, 1895 Dec. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Apr. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 May 15; 1p.
  - Films for Democracy (Box 27)
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec.; 4p.
  - Financial Report (Box 27)
    - 1929-30 Dec., 1p.
    - 1939 Feb-Mar, 1p
  - Findeisen, H. (Box 27)
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 28; 1p.
  - Findley, P.B. (Box 27)
    - To Boas, 1925 June 16; 1p.
  - Fink, Reuben (Box 27)
    - To Boas, 1919 May 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 July 1; 1p.
  - Finkelstein, Louis (Box 27)
    - From Boas, 1940 June 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 July 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 July 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Jan. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 July 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 May 28; 1p.
    - (Enc: Conference on science, philosophy and religion in their relation to the democratic way of life; List of founding members of conference, May 21, 1940)
    - To Boas, 1940 June 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 June 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 July 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 July 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Sept. 19; 1p.
  - Finkelstein, Moses I. (Box 27)
    - From Boas, 1941 July 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Dec. 22
    - (see Boas, F. to Rautenstrauch, W., Dec. 22, 1941)
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Aug. 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Sept. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 July 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 July 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 July 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 July 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Aug. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Aug. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Aug. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Aug. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Aug. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Sept. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Sept.
    - (see Finkelstein, M.I. to Dearborn...), 1941 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Aug. 18; 1p.
    - M.I. Finkelstein -- to C.A. Beard
      - (Enc: Boas, F. to Aldrich, Winthrop Aldrich, W.W., July 28, 1939 Aug. 1, 1939)
    - M.I. Finkelstein -- to C.A. Beard, 1939 Aug. 13; 1p.
    - M.I. Finkelstein -- to B. Colwell Davis, 1939 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - M.I. Finkelstein -- to Dearborn, Boas, and Rautenstrauch, 1941 Sept; 2p.
    - M.I. Finkelstein -- to B.C. Edel, 1942 Oct. 25; 1p.
    - M.I. Finkelstein -- to L.M. Hanks, Jr., 1942 June 4; 2p.
    - M.I. Finkelstein -- to A. Lefkowitz, 1939 Oct. 21; 1p.
    - M.I. Finkelstein -- to W. Rautenstrauch
      (see Finkelstein, M.I. to Dearborn...)
    - M.I. Finkelstein -- to W. Rautenstrauch, 1941 Sept.
    - M.I. Finkelstein -- to H. Shapley, 1941 Oct. 10; 1p.
    - M.I. Finkelstein -- from Stewart, Maxwell S., 1940 Dec. 4
  - Finley, J.C. (Box 27)
    - From Boas, 1921 Oct. 24; 1p.
  - Finley, John H. (Box 27)
    - From Boas, 1908 May 19
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 31; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 29; 1p.
      (Enc: Extract from a letter from Dr. Graves)
    - J.H. Finley -- from Dr. Graves
      - (Extract from a letter from Dr. Graves. See Finley J.H., Dec. 29, 1921)
  - Finneran, John T. (Box 27)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 18
    - (see Boas, F. to Kep el, F.P., Jan. 18, 1939)
  - Finnie, O.S. (Box 27)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 5; 1p.
  - Finsch, Otto (Box 27)
    - To Boas, 1894 June 5; 1p,
    - To Boas, 1894 July 2
    - To Boas, 1897 Feb. 18; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1897 May 10; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1897 June 8; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1897 Oct. 24; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1897 Oct. 28; 2p.
  - Firben, A.L. (Box 27)
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 8; 1p.
  - Fischberg, Dr. Maurice (Box 27)
    - To Boas, 1903 June 17
  - Fischel, Alfred (Box 27)
    - From Boas, 1920 May 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 July 21; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 June 28; 4p.
  - Fischer, Eugen (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 4
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Jan. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Aug. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 July 23
    - To Boas, 1902 Nov. 26
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 10
    - To Boas, 1904 July 9
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 10; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 30; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 25
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 July 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Feb. 2; 8p.
    - To Boas, 1928 July 9
      (cablegram)
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 27; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 July 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 July 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 June 24; 1p.
  - Fischer, Gustav (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Sept. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 July 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 July 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 May 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 17; 1p.
      (Enc: Receipt)
  - Fischer, Hermann (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 June 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 June 5; 2p.
  - Fischer, Karl (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 16-18
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 11; 2p.
  - Fischer, Theobald (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1878 Feb. 21
    - To Boas, 1878 Feb. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1882 Mar. 31
    - To Boas, 1882 Apr. 3
    - To Boas, 1882 May 26
    - To Boas, 1882 July 24
    - To Boas, 1883 June 5
    - To Boas, 1884 Nov. 2; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1885 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1885 June 5
    - To Boas, 1885 June 19
    - To Boas, 1885 July 4
    - To Boas, 1885 July 25
    - To Boas, 1885 July 28
    - To Boas, 1885 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1885 Nov. 21
    - To Boas, 1885 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1886 Jan. 2
    - To Boas, 1886 Feb. 6
    - To Boas, 1886 Feb. 27
    - To Boas, 1886 May 30
    - To Boas, 1886 Oct. 3
    - To Boas, 1887 Mar. 13
    - To Boas, 1893 May 23; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1894 Aug. 29; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1895 Mar. 3
      (postcard)
    - To Boas, 1895 May 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1895 June 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 July 23; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Dec. 26
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 10; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1904 July 9; 2p.
    - Theobald Fischer -- to Toni Boas, 1884 Apr. 3
    - To Boas, 1884 Sept. 7
    - To Boas, 1884 Oct. 26
  - Fischer, O. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 29; 1p.
  - Fish, Joseph B. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1905 May 29
    - To Boas, 1905 May 30
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 16
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1909 May 23
  - Fish, Leon J. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Feb. 15; 1p.
  - Fishberg, Maurice (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1903 Apr. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Aug. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1908 May 29
    - From Boas, 1908 June 6
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 1
    - From Boas, 1909 June 5
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 18
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Apr. 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 June 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 June 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 13
    - To Boas, 1908 May 28
    - To Boas, 1908 June 9
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 27
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1909 June 6
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 19
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 9
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 19
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 8; 1p.
  - Fisher, Allen S. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1934 Aug. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 4; 1p.
  - Fisher, George (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1905 June 27
  - Fisher, Irving (Box 28)
    - From Boas
    - (see Boas, F. to Shipler, G.E., Sept. 17, 1941)
  - Fisher, Robert L. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 11; 1p.
  - Fisher, Sydney G. (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1924 June 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 June 23; 2p.
  - Fishman, Beatrice (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec.; 1p.
    - Fishman, P., 1936 Jan. 17; 1p.
      (Enc: Boas, F. A study of existing records accumulated by the Dept. of Anthropology of the music, art and literature of the American Indian)
  - Fisk Teachers Agencies (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec.; 1p.
  - Fiske, T.S. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1907 May 4
    - To Boas, 1907 May 3
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 20
  - Fite, W.B. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1921 Oct. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 2; 1p.
  - Fitz, G.W. (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1896 Jan. 14
  - Fitz-Gerald, John D. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Dec. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 17
    - To Boas, 1927 June 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 8; 2p.
  - Fitzpatrick, T.S. (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1920 July 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 9; 1p.
  - Flanagan, Hallie (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1936 July 14; 1p.
  - Fleischman (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1908 June 1
  - Fleming, A.L. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 16; 1p.
  - Fleming, A.T. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 7
  - Fleming, D.I. (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1927 July 25; 1p.
      (Enc: McIlwraith, T.F. Some missionary problems from an anthropological viewpoint)
  - Fleming, D.P. (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 10; 1p.
  - Fleming, H.G. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 1
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 13
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 11
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 3
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 22
    - J.A. Fleming -- to A.H. Clarke, 1931 June 6; 1p.
    - Mark L. Fleming -- to Ernst P. Boas, 1933 Oct. 17; 2p.
  - Flemming, Mrs. Cecil White (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1930 May 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 June 8; 1p.
  - Fleschelly, J. (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 27
  - Fletcher (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 15
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 20
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 26
    - To Boas, 1902 Oct. 14
    - To Boas, 1902 Nov. 6
    - To Boas, 1902 Nov. 21
    - To Boas, 1903 July 2
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 19
    - To Boas, 1905 Sept. 5
  - Fletcher, Alice C. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 19
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 24
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 3; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 6; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 29; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1894 July 28
    - To Boas, 1895 Apr. 6
    - To Boas, 1895 Oct. 30
    - To Boas, 1895 Dec. 14
    - To Boas, 1896 Jan. 2
    - To Boas, 1896 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1896 July 15
    - To Boas, 1896 Oct. 26
    - To Boas, 1896 Oct. 29
    - To Boas, 1896 Nov. 13
    - To Boas, 1896 Nov. 14
    - To Boas, 1896 Nov. 26
    - To Boas, 1897 May 22; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1897 Oct. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Jan. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1898 July 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Aug. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Oct. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Nov. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Nov. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 July 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 22; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 17
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 20
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 30
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 12
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 16
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 19; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 2
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1911 May 2
    - Miss A.C. Fletcher -- from A.M. Tozzer, May 8, 1911
  - Fletcher, Harvey (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1925 May 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 May 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 May 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 May 10; 1p.
  - Fletcher, Robert (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1899 June 5; 1p.
    - Robert Fletcher -- to F.W. Hodge, 1899 June 5; 2p.
  - Fleure, H.J. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 27; 1p.
  - Flexner, Abraham (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 28
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 12; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 17; 1p.
    - (see Boas, F. to Shipler, G.E. Sept. 17,1941, 1941 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 5
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - (Enc: Arnett, T to Flexner, A. Nov. 14,1927), 1927 Nov. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 22; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec.
      (see Baker, Frank E. open letter)
    - (see Boas, F. open letter July 18, 1941), 1941 Oct. 24; 1p.
    - A. Flexner -- from T. Arnett
      - (Enc Flexner, A., Nov. 16, 1927)
    - A. Flexner -- from T. Arnett, 1927 Nov. 14
    - A. Flexner -- to G. McAneny
      - (Enc: originally with McAneny, G. to Boas, F., May 28, 1918)
    - A. Flexner -- to G. McAneny, 1918 May 24; 1p.
    - A. Flexner -- to C.R. Miller, 1939 July 10
    - A. Flexner -- to J. Sachs, 1918 May 1; 1p.
  - Flexner, B. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 5; 1p.
  - Flexner, Simon (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 2
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 May 26; 1p.
  - Fligelman, F. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1930 June 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 30; 1p.
    - (enc. originally with Barnes, H.E. July 8, 1918), 1930 Feb. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 May 26; 1p.
      (Enc: Moral vocabulary of an unwritten language Fulani Sample pages)
  - Flink, S. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1935 Sept. 12; 1p.
      (Enc: Notes re Carl von Ossietzky)
  - Flint (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1898 Dec. 1
    - From Boas, 1898 Dec. 1
  - Flint, Earl (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1887 July 23
  - Flint, Weston (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1898 Nov. 25
    - To Boas, 1898 Nov. 31
  - Flissmid, Erwin (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 4; 1p.
  - Flynn, J.T. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1938 June 17; 1p.
  - Fulcomer, Miss Anne (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1896 May 7
  - Fulscher, H. (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1881 Aug. 5
  - Focke, E. (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1924 Jan. 26; 4p.
      (Enc: Nachtrag)
  - Foehl, A., Jr. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 4; 1p.
  - Foerd (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 5
  - Foerster, R. (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1920 Jan. 2; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 17; 1p.
  - Fogel, Edwin M. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 4
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 14
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 June 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Sept. 24
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 13
  - Fohs, F.J. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 May 29; 1p.
    - (Enc: Fohs, F.J. to members National committee list of American committee on science and technology, Hebrew University. Schack, W. Four years of the Hebrew Univ.), 1931 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - F.J. Fohs -- to members of the National Committee of American committee of science and technology, Hebrew Univ.), 1929 May 16; 1p.
  - Foldaweiser, A. (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1909 Aug. 29
  - Foley, John (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1936 Sept. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Oct. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Nov. 21; 1p.
  - Foley, J.P., Jr. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 17; 1p.
  - Folkers, T. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1934 Sept. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 11; 1p.
  - Folkierski, W. (Box 28)
    - W. Folkierski -- to Société des nations. Institut international de coopération de intellectuale. Sections des relations scientifiques, 1928 Oct. 13; 2p.
  - Folk-lore (Box 28)
    - To Boas from Pound, L., 1923; 1p.
    - Folklore Journal, 1916 Dec.
      (see Boas, F.)
  - Folsom, Cora M. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 26
    - From Boas, 1909 May 8; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 May 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 May 18
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 21
    - To Boas, 1905 Sept. 19
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 13
    - To Boas, 1907 May 16
    - To Boas, 1907 May 20
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 23; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1909 May 12
  - Folsom, Franklin (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 15; 1p.
  - Fontain, H. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1912 May 20; 2p.
  - Foord (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 21
  - Ford, Clellan S. (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1940 May 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 June 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Aug. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 17; 1p.
  - Ford, Guy S. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1939 May 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 10
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 10; 1p.
  - Ford, John B. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1915 Dec. 10; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 June 24; 1p.
  - Form for measurement of arm (Box 28)
    - 1939 Oct., 1p.
  - Formby, J. (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1915 July 2
  - Forrestly, J. (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 9
  - Forsey, F.E. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1931 Sept. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Sept. 18; 1p.
  - Forstein, A.S. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 30; 3p.
  - Fort-Whiteman, Lovett (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - (Enc: Fort-Whiteman, Lovett, Nov. 7, 1927)
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - (Enc with Boas, F. to Fort-Whiteman, L.), Nov. 9, 1927
  - Fortier, A. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1908 June 12
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 7
    - To Boas, 1892 Mar. 25
    - To Boas, 1908 June 16
  - Fortune, Reo F. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1934 May 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 July 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Sept. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Sept. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 May 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 June 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 June 30; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1942 May 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 July 14; 4p.
    - (see Boas, F., Mar. 18, 1929)
    - (see Boas, F. To Columbia Univ. Committee on fellowships, Feb. 27, 1930)
    - (see Boas, F., Mar. 18, 1930)
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 10; 6p.